<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[elev8 .*. anünaka]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[elev8 .*. anünaka]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/anaka/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 04:35:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/anaka/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[With the universal access of phone photography,]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>With the universal access of phone photography,</h1><p> the citizen’s interaction with documenting surreal experiences creates a uniquely authentic archive. This infinitely growing archive is used as a window for the world to spiritually experience another person’s authentic moment almost in real time, increasing communal transparency on a global scale. The ability to document the natural magic of the world with photography already bends space and time spirituality, and the global access to do so with phone cameras creates global conscious transparency. However, using a phone during a healing moment can arguably spiritually dilute the soul’s experience. In this generation, with the constant push of technology as a way of life, we must use technology in situations in order to further our communal knowledge, instead of solely indulge in our individual egotistical habits.  </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/anaka/with-the-universal-access-of-phone-photography/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">442b645a-8e11-4690-bb52-d11d30408ae3</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 04:35:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[“Yes, and the body has memory. The physical carriage hauls more than its weight. The body is the threshold across which each objectionable call passes into consciousness—all the unintimidated, unblinking, and unflappable resilience does not erase the moments lived through, even as we are eternally stupid or everlastingly optimistic, so ready to be inside, among, a part of the games.”]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>“Yes, and the body has memory. The physical carriage hauls more than its weight. The body is the threshold across which each objectionable call passes into consciousness—all the unintimidated, unblinking, and unflappable resilience does not erase the moments lived through, even as we are eternally stupid or everlastingly optimistic, so ready to be inside, among, a part of the games.”</h1><p>Dear future homestay family in Cape Town, SA,</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/anaka/yes-and-the-body-has-memory-the-physical-carriage-hauls-m/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">11bd6f07-f44d-4846-8ef0-df6ce877d4e3</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 07:59:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>